http://www.templeisraelva.org/privacy-statement

Privacy Statement
Temple Israel is committed to safeguarding your privacy online.
Voluntary Submission
Temple Israel does not collect personally identifying information about any individual site visitor except when knowingly provided by such individual.
For example, we may ask you for information, such as your e-mail address, zip code, etc. in order to receive requested information such as a brochure or newsletter. You always have the option not to provide the information we request. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of our site.
Cookies
We currently use, and may use in the future, the following types of cookies on this website.
We use session cookies to:
help us maintain security and verify your details whilst you use the website as you navigate from page to page, which enables you to avoid having to re-enter your details each time you enter a new page.
We use persistent cookies to:
help us recognise you as a unique user when you return to our website so that you do not have to input your details multiple times as you move between our pages or services
remember how you have customised your use of this site, such as your preferred currency and time zone
collect and compile anonymous, aggregated information for statistical and evaluation purposes to help us understand how users use the website and help us improve the structure of our website.
Many cookies are designed to give you optimal usage of the web. For example, we use cookies to enable you to improve your user experience when using our website, e.g. a cookie which recognises if your browser supports specific technology features. This helps, for example, in enabling web pages to be loaded more quickly when you request the download of a large file.
In addition to cookies which send information to us, we also use cookies which collect information and send it to third parties. An example of this is Google Analytics. Please check the relevant third party website for more information about their use of cookies. Where this site allows such cookies to be set or you access other websites from this site using the links provided, the operators of these websites will use cookies in accordance with their own cookies policy, which may differ from ours.
As with first party cookies, you are able to block third party cookies through your browser settings.
Some of our cookies may collect and store your personal information, such as your name or email address. We are committed to respecting and protecting your privacy and will ensure that all personal information collected by us is kept and treated in accordance with our privacy policy. A link to this policy is available within the footer of this portal.
Sharing of Information
When you are on an area of Temple Israel’s web site and submit data, please be aware that no personally identifiable information provided by our visitors will be shared with third parties or advertisers unless otherwise posted or requested.
As Required By Law
Temple Israel may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on our site or to protect and defend the rights or property of Temple Israel.
Privacy of Children Kids under 13:
Do not send any information about yourself to us–including information such as your name, address, or e-mail address. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.
Pop Up Advertisement Disclaimer
Any Pop-Up advertisements you may be seeing on this web site are not coming from the Temple Israel’s Web Site. The advertisements are not generated by Temple Israel and we have not contracted with anyone for such advertisement services. Some Internet sites are programmed to create Pop-up windows when you exit them. When you visit the Temple Israel website after surfing these websites, you may experience Pop-up windows on the screen. Also, some free ware programs that you may have installed on your system may cause these Pop-up windows. These programs (for example: Music and File sharing) support themselves by agreeing to install advertising packages with their product.
Contact Info
(757) 489-4550
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Temple Israel7255 Granby StreetNorfolk, VA 23505
Home page
About Us
Contact us
Never been here before?
© 2020 Temple Israel in Norfolk, VA - Conservative Jewish Synagogue Open To All
|
All Rights Reserved
|
Website development by OCCS
